<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ArminianExpresApp</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_search">Search</string>
    <string name="ayvazyan_95_mail_ru">Ayvazyan.95@mail.ru</string>
    <string name="_37495666700">,+37495666700</string>
    <string name="ip5s_desc">"Apple iPhone 5s smartphone was launched in September 2013. The phone comes with a 4.00-inch touchscreen"
        "display with a resolution of 640 pixels by 1136 pixels at a PPI of 326 pixels per inch. Apple iPhone 5s price in India"
        "starts from Rs. 16,899."</string>
    <string name="samsungs8">,"Samsung Galaxy S8 smartphone was launched in March 2017. The phone comes with a 5.80-inch touchscreen"
        "display with a resolution of 1440 pixels by 2960 pixels at a PPI of 570 pixels per inch."
        Samsung Galaxy S8 price in India starts from Rs. 41,990*."</string>
    <string name="ifonX">,"Our vision has always been to create an iPhone that is entirely screen. One so immersive the device itself disappears into the experience"
        ".And so intelligent it can respond to a tap, your voice, and even a glance."
        "With iPhone X, that vision is now a reality. Say hello to the future."</string>
    <string name="nikolay">,"If you want add a difference to the” all black” – look, this watch will give you what you’re looking for,"
        "a case in stainless steel and gold details, gives the classic look a twist."
        "Limited lifetime warranty"
         "Lars Larsen Watches are celebrating the Nordic high standards by taking all "
      " production in-house and offering the owners of a Lars Larsen watch Limited lifetime warranty/"</string>
    <string name="rloex">,"Rolex watches are crafted from the finest raw materials and assembled with scrupulous attention to detail."
        "Every component is designed, developed and produced in-house to the most exacting standards."</string>
    <string name="apple">,
        "Single Tour
"The classic Hermès design. The buckle recalls those on the straps of a horse’s girth, a nod to the equestrian heritage of Hermès."
        "Available in Fauve Barenia leather paired with 38mm and 42mm stainless steel cases and Indigo Swift leather with a 42mm stainless steel case. "
        "Bands in additional colors available separately."
 .</string>
    <string name="hp">,"The System Information tool is a utility that displays information that is specific to your computer."
        "It displays the Product Name and Product Number which you will need to download drivers or software."
        "It lists some of the hardware specifications for the computer, such as processor type and processor speed and amount of RAM. "
        "If you want more detailed specifications, see the Where can I find a product specifications document? section below."</string>
    <string name="mac">,This article is about the Apple notebook computer called "MacBook" sold until February 2012. For the current notebook computer, see MacBook (12-inch)."
        "For the family of notebook computers designed by Apple first released in 2006, see MacBook family."
"The MacBook is a brand of notebook computers manufactured by Apple Inc. from May 2006 to February 2012, and relaunched in 2015. "
       " It replaced the iBook series and 12-inch PowerBook series of notebooks as a part of the Apple-Intel transition from PowerPC. "
       " Positioned as the low end of the MacBook family, below the premium ultra-portable MacBook Air and the powerful MacBook Pro,[1] the MacBook was aimed at the consumer and education markets."
        "[2] It was the best-selling Macintosh ever. "
       " For five months in 2008, it was the best-selling laptop of any brand in US retail stores.[3] Collectively,"
        "the MacBook brand is the "world's top-selling line of premium laptops."[4]"</string>
    <string name="samsung">",Take your entertainment to the next level and watch the world come to life on the Samsung Notebook 3 vibrant Full HD resolution display."
        "It makes your content nearly twice as sharp as most HD displays on the market." </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_info">" "</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="nomer">+37495666700</string>
</resources>
